MOUELHI MOHAMED FAKHREDDINE

Senior Engineering Student

+216 23 773 777

© Portfolio

in LinkedIn

GitHub

Senior student of computer science at the Private Polytechnic Central School of Tunis. I am a web development enthusiast with much love for the field. I'm committed to creating Web solutions, I possess excellent visual and conceptualization abilities enabling me to visualize and create beautiful and fluid user interfaces and user experiences appealing to stakeholders and design teams.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Full Stack Developer, Bank of Tunisia

Tunis, Tunisia | 10/2022 - present

Developing a branches management and monitoring web application for network admin using Angular and NestJs framework.

Full Stack Developer, Bank of Tunisia

Tunis, Tunisia / 09/2022 - 10/2022

Developed a branch monitoring interface with ping functionality using Angular and NestJs framework.

Front End developer, Hortensia Agency

Tunis, Tunisia / 08/2021-10/2021

Learned front end fundamentals and Angular framework for making fluid UIs.

EDUCATION

Computer Science Engineering | Private Polytechnic Central School of Tunis

Tunis, Tunisia / 2020 – present

Bachelor in Civil Engineering | Higher Institute of Technological Studies of Nabeul

Nabeul, Tunisia / 2020

SKILLS

Computer Science and Softwares

• Programming languages: JavaScript, TypeScript, Python

• Front-End: HTML, CSS, Angular

Back-end: NestJsDataBase: MysqlVersion control: Git

• Modeling Language: UML

Languages

• English: Aptis-C

• French: Professional competence

• Arabic: Native

ACTIVITIES AND INTERESTS

Activities

E-Health valley 2022 | Hackathon

Tunis, Tunisia | 29/09/2022 - 30/09/2022

Digital solution for at supply management of drug stocks, synchronizing and improving the exchange of information between the parties involved in order to improve access to drugs and prevent stock shortages.

Teaching | freelance

Tunis, Tunisia | August 2022 - present

Teaching HTML, CSS and JavaScript fundamentals to high school pupils.

Interests

Technology and Entrepreneurship: As a software engineer student, I am always interested in all related topics to the latest technologies, inventions, Startups.